Thank you for your time
We're here.
What time is it?
I don't know. I don't have my phone.
I don't see a clock.
It's about midnight.
I haven't been to Sakura House since Zelkova House.
About 5 years?
We all barbecued together.
Barbecue?
One of us bought some groceries, so...
Thank you very much.
I'm about to start filming.
Will it be the last one?
Yes, let's make some memories.
Let's take a picture.
What's the house like?
I'll open it.
Wow, what a surprise!
That's hard.
Wow, that's great.
Please.
It's so wide.
Oh, my God.
I'll put the ingredients down for a while.
When we were at the cake house...
There was a TV here.
I think there was a sofa.
There's a kitchen over here.
There's a pool over here.There's a pool over here.
Pool!
There's a pool.
There's a pool. It's glowing.
It's a blue pool.
It looks like a barrel.
It's real.
It's all the rage now.
Maybe I'll go in when it gets colder.
Saunas are all the rage at the store.
I'm glad.
It's 1.1 meters deep.
Rina, can you go?
You want me to introduce you?
This way.
This is a barbecue set.
Twenty pounds.
That's great.
Steak 1,800 yen.
That's right.
Habe-chan chose
Sausage
Five kinds!
Wow, there were two!
Honey is the upper arm
I'm full!
Teppan is here.
Kao-chan said there's a teppan!
It's an anvil!
We can make weapons!I could make weapons.
What?
I found some yakisoba griddles.
You still have this in the freezer?
Fries and cheese balls.
You know, the fries and cheese balls that you give them.
Yes, I got it.
Wait a minute. Oil.
Turn the heat dial to the left while pressing it.
and light the pipe with the Chuckerman.
Here's the Chuckerman.
Put it in.
Yes, sir.
a. And hold it more...
Just enough oil to cover it.
Hidden.
That's right.
I think I found it.
It's right there.
Yes, yes, yes.
I thought I saw it somewhere.
What?
You scared the shit out of me.
I thought you were invisible.
That's scary.
Please, please, please.Yes, please.
Yes, sir.
Watch the oil. Here we go.
Oh, my God.
Wait, wait, wait. It's hot.
It tastes better when it's empty.
Mmm.
We're making burgers.
Swimmer. It's so fast.
It burns, but...
I honestly feel like I'm getting a little burnt on the edges.
It's a little low on heat.
Uh, I don't think we have any heat.
This one, too? Turn it to the right and it's better.
I turned on the light in here.
It's so bright.
This one's kind of nice, too.
Oh, it's broken.
How's that?
Oh, it's good, right?
Let's take a look inside.
Ta-da!
Wow, it's done.
All right.
Potatoes are so good.
I love it, I love it, I love it.
And they're kind of...
I want you guys to give me a compliment.
I'm just trying to get a compliment from both of you.
How do you like them?How's it look?
Wow!
That's what I'm talking about!
I'll have Rina-chan and Bubu-chan say how great I am!
Okay, it's done!
It's done!
Okay, let's go!
Potatoes are ready!
Thank you so much!
I'm sorry you had to go through all that trouble.
Oil.
It's electric.
I have work to do.
I have to do it right.
A sense of mission
Sense of responsibility
I'm a responsible person.
I can do it.
What about the fried noodles?
At the same time?
No, we'll have it last.
I thought of it as the end of the meal.
Like this.
Wait.
Can we finish the sausage?
Yes, it'll work. - Yes, on everyone's plate.
One by one, one by one.
But put all the sausages on this one and take them off.
Okay.Oh, okay.
With the sausage.
We'll eat it once? While it's still warm.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Oh.
Okay, Hanyu-chan, please.
Thank you all for your hard work.
Thanks for all your hard work.
Wishing you all the best.
You're breathing really hard.
Cheers. Good job.
Good work. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Bon appétit.
Mm-hmm.
Mmm, it's true.
I wish the five of us could do it together.
Do you think it's a Coke, Mi-chan?
Yeah, a Coke, right, Mi-chan?
Coke on top of Mi-chan.
I'm sorry.
Let's save this.
It's my birthday, but when I made Mi-chan's Coke...
I'll let you rest for a while.
That's right.
Yay!
I'll use this.
Here's your Coke, Mi-chan.
Cheers, Mi-chan.
Cheers, Mi-chan!Cheers, Mi-chan!
Cheers to the five of us!
He's so cute!
Cheers! Cheers! Cheers!
Well, let's eat while it's still warm. Thank you.
Hari, your potatoes look terrible. They're not salted yet.
Aren't they crispy?
Is this how you do it?
I feel like I'm missing something. It's all together, but it's good.
Delicious.
I'm really hungry.
I'm starving.
Yeah, and I'm not really hungry.
But when you start eating like this, you get hungry.
But there are five of us now. We're alive.
Who would have guessed?
I've been told. It's about time.
Eight?
That's great. Eight?
Yes, eight.
Eight lives.
You're very popular.
Thank you.
Oh, I feel like I'm looking at a summer food truck.
Hey. Hey.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Come on, come on, come on.Hi, honey.
Yeah.
Here we go.
One steak, please.
Yes, one steak, please.
She's a great girl.
Is it tough in the summer?
About 1,000 steaks a day in summer.
A thousand?
Yes, that's right.
It's a very limited quantity, isn't it?
Yes, but...
But, the ones we make over here...
Not at all.
It looks bad. It looks really bad.
What is it?
Fat?
Oh, this? This? This?
I don't think so.
Oh, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, man.
This is bad.
Senpai
Oh, yeah?
Did I eat a sausage?
I thought you were quiet.
Palmer.
Halloween girl is making Halloween steaks.
Let's get some shots.Let's take a shot, let's take a shot
Halloween
Is the oil bad?
Put it over here, put it over here. It's better to cut it a little bit.
Bon appétit.
Is it good?
It's really good, but I think one bowl of this is probably too much.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is about right.
Maybe two is my limit.
It depends on who you ask.
But I'm sure the way people are saying it...
Is this seasoned?
Maybe you should put some on.
Maybe I should put some on.
Kabu-chan picked it.
Kabu-chan chose
Some kind of sauce
Only for the price
Only the price is right.
Chuu, too, please.
Here you go.
Okay. Thank you.
Ten.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Is this the enemy?
Unlike the trypan, it's going to go out through the cracks.
That's for sure.
Careful.
Oh, twisting?
It's warm! It's warm!
Take your camera with you.
It's warm!
Take the camera.
Warm, warm.
Sauna.
Oh, my God, it's just a little bit...
It's so warm It's so cold It's so cold
Thank God! Don't leave this place!
I ate yakisoba here!
Yakisoba!
It pisses me off!
The one in the sauna.
Is it ready? It looks good.
Come and get it.
You want to get it?
Yeah, come get it.
Look at Mayu. Rina's serious.
Oh, my gosh!
It's amazing!
It's so shiny!
In the kitchen?
I knew it!
I liked your eye water jar, didn't I?I liked the eye watering can, didn't I?
Yeah.
We should all eat station noodles.
Here you go, four.
Sure thing.
Here they are.
Sure, sure.
I said I didn't know if we'd be able to eat it, but I divided it into four portions.
Okay, well, I'll just take these.
You can all go ahead and take... all of it.
No, wait, the last one is the best.
You don't take a lot of the edges.
Here's a sexy shot.
Hold the yakisoba.
It's done!
Here's a sexy shot.
Where are you going to put this?
Don't take the noodles.
Put it on the sausage.
What's the picture?
Hey.
Where?
Sexy shot of the pool.
Pool and yakisoba.
Bon appétit.
Yum!
Bon appétit!
Looks good!
Here we go.Come on, come on, come on.
Let's go around in a minute.
Don't look, don't look, don't look.
I'm not gonna look at my watch.
Me neither.
Time limit.
It's warm.
My left hand is cold, my right hand is hot.
Go take a sauna.
Mmm. - Mmm.
Is it good?
It's good.
Yum.
Tasty.
Yum. - Yum.
Yeah. - Yeah.
There's too much meat on this yakisoba.
I had the yabasoba.
Not a single vegetable. I ended up with a lot of vegetables.
If you like, you can put a sunchu on it.
Thank you!
There's some left.
I'm the best.
But I thought of you the other night at the bottom of the fence.
Habu-chan? Habu wasn't there.
I thought I was missing something, but it was Habu-chan.
I got it!
I want to heat it up inside
The windows are open all the time.I'll keep the window open.
Thank you. Thank you.
Are you okay?
You look like a total bitch.
I'll fill you up.
Thank you.
I'm afraid it's going to dry up really bad tomorrow.
Shiny.
I woke up this morning. There are two beds there.
We'll stop when it warms up.
Three beds?
There were four.
No, I'm good. I'm good. I'm good.
Me, me, me, me.
Oh, my God.
I hope someone's awake.
You want me to call you?
Hey.
Kira's been up all night.
What did Kira say when I called her earlier?
Oh! Let's try.
Doesn't it look like she's not going to answer it? This one. It won't come out right away.
Were you sleeping?
Please don't turn on the camera.
Did you sleep?
I was here once.
Were you practicing for tomorrow?
Who was that?
Who do you think?
Maybe he can see us from there. Maybe he can see us from there.
What's going on?
Oh, you see it?
What?
What? Is this now?
Right now?
You're eating dinner right now?
Yes, I am.
Don't eat late at night.
Of course not.
What can I get you?
I'm not hungry.
I only had egg itch rice for dinner tonight.
Yesterday, there was an omelette and rice dish on the news.
I thought yesterday that I wanted to eat egg itchy rice, so I had it today.
You sound sleepy.
See you tomorrow.
Good luck!
Sleep well.
I'll see you in my dreams.
I'll try my best to sleep.
Definitely sleep... and good luck.
Good night.
Thank you.
I'll see you in my dreams.
Yeah, yeah.
Yes, ma'am.
Good night.Good night.
Congratulations on your hot box!
Thank you.
I'll see you in my dreams.
See you later.
Good night.
It's cold.
Okay, sauna.
Can you fit four people in there?
Yeah, four.
Are you done?
Are they gone?
Yeah, I'm in.
I did the sauna content.
It's warm.
It's great!
I wish we could take pictures of the pool.
It's so warm
Good night.
I knew you'd like it here.
We do.
Yeah, we do.
It makes me feel at home.
It's nighttime. - What?
Hey, it's cold in here.
It's cold in here?
It's absolutely freezing. Absolutely freezing.Absolutely cold. Absolutely cold.
Excuse me for a second.
I just want to get a foot in the camera over here.
I'm sorry.
Try shadows with your feet.
What? Just a little bit.
We've done shadows.
I did, too.
What? With Yuri?
I didn't do it.
You did.
Is that the third Anila?
What Anila?
Budokan.
The Budokan.
So...
That's the Anila after Osaka.
I don't remember what anila.
This is my sixth Anila.
That's amazing!
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God.
How many weeks? Anila.
3?
2 weeks?
Not even 3?
Two weeks.
I was surprised when I saw the calendar.I was surprised when I saw the calendar.
It's so close.
That's why it's so...
For Hug-chan...
For Hug, it's just after Anila.
For you...
It's until graduation.
That's true.
I'm sure the days feel very different.
So fast... so fast...
It's so fast from the announcement to graduation.
What? When did we announce it to the world?
In August.
Oh, that's fine.
February.
It felt like a long time ago.
Yeah, that's right... this year.
I'll be working on it in a few years or something.
Like the Oujikai.
We're going to get together and do something.
It's nice to get together, but I don't think we'll be able to dance anymore
I'll see you at the Nohgi-san
The 10th anniversary of Nogi-san...
Oh, yeah, sure, it's a big deal
Hypnotherapist already is.
The witch is...
You're still showing your kids your wife's quizzes.
I'm not happy.
You know, that first one.
Grandma, Grandma!Grandma, grandma, grandma.
The very first one.
That look on your face...
Stop it. Stop it.
Oh, no.
The look on your face.
The face you make when you wake up.
It's so fast... ouch... ouch...
I remember that face of Erina's.
Why?
Heson talk
Patsun's face
Patzun's
It's so blinding.
It's so bright when you wake up from sleep.
I love it.
I'm glad it's still on film.
Yeah.
I don't know.
It's amazing.
Everyone can share and talk.
Sharing.
We handed out posters and leaflets, right?
So those who have recently come to know us don't know about that either.
Also, they don't know about the new makeup artist.
Did you do that?
Yes, we did. Free handshakes.
What was it? Guerrilla?
I remember.
Fuu-chan should be saved. You should save Fuu-chan.
She's laughing so hard.
What time is it?
Let me guess, 2:30.
Too close.
2:25.
2:00...what?
It's got to be 40 minutes.
Two, two, three.
Well, it's time for me to go to bed.
Lately, I wake up in the middle of the night and look at the clock and it's 444.
Oh, no.
I'm too synchronized.
It's great.
It definitely tastes better after a bath.
It's cold right now.
It's cold.
I can't do it anymore.
I think I'll boil a bath.
I'll tell you.
Well, well, well.
And, and, and, and...
Okay, everyone.
Did the glass fall?
Did it fall?
Thank you for your hard work.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yes, yes, yes.Yay.
Bon appétit.
Abu-chan's special.
Yum.
Ah!
Refreshing, right?
Here we go.
And that's that.
Thank you for your hard work.
for all your hard work.
One after the other
Let's play rock-paper-scissors-paper in the bath!
I'm really good at rock-paper-scissors-paper.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Who wants to go in first?
Okay, then.
Yay!
You made yakisoba.
I'll do it.
Want to play rock-paper-scissors in the bath?
Sure.
I don't care what number.
Let's go for number two.
Yay.
Let's go number three.
Okay, those taking a bath, you're in.
Those of you who clean up, clean up.
All right.All right.
Good morning. Good morning.
Good morning
In the morning.
And by morning, I mean fireworks.
Wow!
Rina's Calpis Chua
Green
So cute!
I'm hungry
Hungry
I'm hungry.
What's with the camera?
Yay.
I really feel like it was my youth, and
I'm going to miss it even more after graduation
Who's that mumbling?
It was Ham and Rina.
Good night.